

Esmaeil Jafari

FRONT END DEVELOPER

tehran,tehran

esmaeiljafari1992@gmail.com

in @esmaeil-jafari1992

PROFILE

birthday 16 June 1992

I am a front-end developer with a proven ability to collaborate effectively with senior developers. I always enjoy working as a team member. I have a strong passion and Interested in learning new technologies, and using them, adhering to the ethics and rules of each set Experience working in programming teams and coordinating with colleagues

SKILLS

Javascript Git
Typescript Html5
React is Css3

Next js Jauery

Jqueiy

Redux

Bootstrap

Tailwind

Sass

WordPress

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Ketab Plus

Mar 2020 - Present

KetabPlus is a Start-Up in the Field Of Books Whose Target Is To Encourage People To Buy Books And Read More . (https://ketabplus.com)

My Responsibility is Refactor . Develop and Maintain the WebSite and also its Panel.

TypeScript | Next js | React | Redux-Tookit | ReactBootstrp | TailWind | SASS | WordPress

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Sandbadcell

Aug 2019 - Feb 2020

Sandbadcell is a platform for major online commerce that connects manufacturers all over Iran directly to major buyers of products from various industries . (https://www.sandbadcell.com)

I have been present since the establishment of this company and I was responsible for building the site and the customer management panel and the site management panel with the following technologies and software

Jquery | React | Redux | ReactBootstrap | Bootstrap | Wordpress | PHP

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Seoraz

Feb 2017 - Aug 2019

Seoraz is a fully bundled services provider of Web Design, Development, Corporate identity, Mobile Apps along with SEO and Social Media. We use to work on ecommerce websites, CMSes, large databases for clients world-wide.(seoraz.com)

My responsibility in seoraz is to design the templates of a number of WordPress sites and to create the site and panel of the following sites: https://poshtebam.com

https://simagar.com

http://www.karsima.com

Jquery | React | Bootstarp | Php | WordPress | OpenCart | joomla | PhotoShop

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Web Negah

Jan 2015 - Jan 2017

WebNegah is a programming Company With 20 Years Of Experience inThis Field . My Responsibility in This Company Was to Design Websites According to Customer Needs. (webnegah.com)

The projects I did on the web included WordPress projects and https://jiet.app

That builds the site and its admin panel

Wordpress / DNN / SEO / JavaScript / JQuery | Bootstrap | OpenCart | PhotoShop

WEB DESIGNER

Vira

Jan 2014 - Jan 2015

vira a digital marketing site

My Responsibility is change ui and content in some Wordpress sites $html\ /\ css\ /\ wordpress$

EDUCATION HISTORY

Bachelor of *Computer science* payam noor Varamin